我们将从建立我们的Sunshine数据库
We will begin building our database for
来定义我们的天气合约
Sunshine by defining our weather contract.
你可能会问  什么是合约
You might ask, what is a contract?
合约就是一个数据模型  存储
A contract is an agreement between the data model, storage, and
视图  展示以及描述信息如何被访问的协议
views, presentation, describing how information is accessed.
合约的一致性在合约类中执行
The agreement in a contract is implemented in a contract class that
这个合约类包括一个常量的列表  通常还有数据库表和列的名称
contains a list of constants, typically database table column names, that
这些被用来和一个应用的UI数据源进行数据交互
are used to associate data from the data source within the UI of an application.
所以  假如说这个代表了用户界面  那么下面的这张表
So, if this represents the user interface, then the bottom table
代表了用来给UI提供数据的数据源
represents the data source that is being used to feed data to the UI.
每一列数据源的元素代表了一个UI元素
Each column in the data source represents a UI element.
如果我们在developer.android.com搜索contract这个单词
If we search developer.android.com for the word,
我们可以看到有很多类似的合约
contract, we see that there are many such contracts to find.
举例来说  在联系人合约中
In the Contacts Contract, for example,
我们可以看到合约的一部分包括了一个列名称的列表
we can see that part of the contract contains a list of column names.
并且我们能够了解合约数据库是什么样子
And we can have some sense of what the contact database looks like.
它有一个列作为显示名以及合约的标示符
It has a column for the display name, flags for the contact, columns for
以及存放ID的列并被用来链接其他表里面的数据
ID's that are used to link the contact to data in other tables.
并且还有指向与合约有关的图像的URI列
And columns for URI's that point to images associated with the contact.
在Sunshine中我们的合约是用来创建和
In Sunshine, our contract is used to both create and
与我们的数据库的表交互的
interact with our database tables.
这就是为什么我们需要在创建数据库之初就定义它
Which is why we need to define it at the start of building our database.
当然  为了创建我们的合约
Of course, to create our contract,
我们首先需要知道我们要在数据库中储存什么
we first need to know what we need to store in the database.